Big publishing company. They lost a bunch of money one year, and their executive team for three days visualized their entire practice. And what's interesting is that after visualizing the entire business, systems upon systems, they reclaimed 50 million dollars of revenue, and they also moved from a D rating to an A rating from their customers. Why? Because there's alignment from the executive team. So I'm now on a mission to help organizations solve their wicked problems by using collaborative visualization, and on a site that I've produced called drawtoast.com, I've collected a bunch of best practices. and so you can learn how to run a workshop here, you can learn more about the visual language and the structure of links and nodes that you can apply to general problem-solving, and download examples of various templates for unpacking the thorny problems that we all face in our organizations. So the seemingly trivial design exercise of drawing toast helps us get clear, engaged and aligned. So next time you're confronted with an interesting challenge, remember what design has to teach us. Make your ideas visible, tangible, and consequential. It's simple, it's fun, it's powerful, and I believe it's an idea worth celebrating. Thank you. (Applause)
Grande maison d'édition. Ils ont perdu beaucoup d'argent une année, et pendant 3 jours leur équipe dirigeante a visualisé toutes leurs méthodes. Ce qui est intéressant, c'est qu'après avoir visualisé toute l'entreprise, système après système, ils ont récupéré 50 millions de dollars de revenus, et sont passés de la catégorie D à A de la part de leurs clients. Pourquoi ? Parce qu'il y a une cohérence au sein de l'équipe exécutive. Ma mission aujourd'hui consiste à aider les organisations à résoudre leurs problèmes épineux avec la visualisation collaborative, et sur un site que j'ai réalisé, drawtoast.com, j'ai collecté plein de bonnes pratiques, pour vous permettre d'y apprendre comment diriger un workshop. Vous pouvez en apprendre plus sur le langage visuel et les structures de liens et nœuds applicables à la résolution de problèmes. et télécharger des exemples de modèles pour déballer les problèmes épineux auxquels nous faisons tous face. Donc l'exercice de design de toast, en apparence trivial, nous aide a être clairs, engagés et cohérents. La prochaine fois que vous serez confrontés à un défi captivant, rappelez-vous ce que nous a appris le design. Rendez vos idées visibles, tangibles et significatives. C'est simple, fun et puissant. Je pense que c'est une idée qui vaut la peine d’être célébrée. Merci. (Applaudissements)